Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 6 and District 6 Locals, 1936-1995 UE.4.1.6
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 6, 1.
  - District 6 Press Releases, June 8, 1942 - May 18, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Press Release Regarding Atomic Energy Commission and Anti-Communism with Sample Leaflet, September 30, 1948; 2. (Box 3, Folder 77, Item 2)
    - Press Release Regarding Taft-Hartley Affidavits and Loney Case, February 11, 1953; 3. (Box 3, Folder 77, Item 3)
    - Press Release Regarding Deportation and McNeil Case, May 18, 1953; 4. (Box 3, Folder 77, Item 4)
  - District 6 Newspaper Clippings, 1937 - 1952 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - U. S. Steel Held in Secret Accord with Lewis Group, 1937; 1. (Box 3, Folder 78, Item 1)
    - Communism in the CIO, Pittsburgh Catholic, June 25, 1942; 2. (Box 3, Folder 78, Item 2)
    - Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, Pittsburgh Catholic, August 6, 1942; 3. (Box 3, Folder 78, Item 3)
    - The Joe Ball Washington Labor Letter, December 10, 1949; 4. (Box 3, Folder 78, Item 4)
    - Loney of the UE Told Off on Reds By CIO Official, Pittsburgh Press, February 27, 1949; 5. (Box 3, Folder 78, Item 5)
    - Four Pro-Commie Suspects Seized, 1952; 6. (Box 3, Folder 78, Item 6)
    - A Public Statement, Pittsburgh Press, undated; 7. (Box 3, Folder 78, Item 7)
    - Overtime Pay and Victory, Pittsburgh Post-Gazette, undated; 8. (Box 3, Folder 78, Item 8)
    - Overtime Pay and Victory, Pittsburgh Sun-Telegraph, undated; 9. (Box 3, Folder 78, Item 9)
    - The Country Editor, undated; 10. (Box 3, Folder 78, Item 10)
  - District 6 Publications and Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - District 6 Publications and Correspondence, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - District 6 Publications and Correspondence, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - District 6 Publication and Correspondence, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - District 6 Publication and Correspondence, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - District 6 Publication and Correspondence, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - District 6 Constitutions, 1942-1951 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - District 6 Constitutions, 1943-1953 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - District 6 Reports on Local Dues and Per Capita Increase, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - District 6 Organizational, Various Plants, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - District 6 Mimeo Material, August 1962 - October 1963 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - District 6 Mimeo Material, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - District 6 Contracts and Grievances, 1980 - 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- District 6 Locals, 2.
  - Local 502
    - Local 502 Constitution, April 9, 1945 - February 1947 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Constitution and By-Laws as Amended, April 9, 1945; 1. (Box 4, Folder 11, Item 1)
      - Constitution and By-Laws as Amended, February 1947; 2. (Box 4, Folder 11, Item 2)
    - Local 502 Officers Lists, December 29, 1941 - June 15, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Local 502 Membership Resolutions, October 14, 1948 - March 17, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Resolution on Anti-Communism and Atomic Energy Commission with October 14, 1948, George Clouser Letter to Julius Emspak, October 11, 1948; 1. (Box 4, Folder 13, Item 1)
      - Resolution on Foreign Policy, Hungary and Bulgaria with March 17, 1949, Ed Ehrensberger Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, March 14, 1949; 2. (Box 4, Folder 13, Item 2)
    - Local 502 Business Agent Larry Ryan Incoming Correspondence, November 12, 1941 - April 27, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Local 502 Constitution, November 28, 1941; 1. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 1)
      - Emspak Telegram Regarding Finances, December 23, 1941; 2. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 2)
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, April 29, 1942; 3. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 3)
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, May 7, 1942; 4. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 4)
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, May 12, 1942; 5. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 5)
      - Emspak Regarding Local 502 Constitution, May 15, 1942; 6. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 6)
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, May 20, 1942; 7. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 7)
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, June 5, 1942; 8. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 8)
      - Emspak Regarding Local 502 Constitution, June 15, 1942; 9. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 9)
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, June 24, 1942; 10. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 10)
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, July 7, 1942; 11. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 11)
      - Emspak Regarding Executive Order 9240 and Overtime, October 5, 1942; 12. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 12)
      - Emspak Regarding Overtime, October 16, 1942; 13. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 13)
      - Emspak Regarding Overtime and Executive Order 9240, November 27, 1942; 14. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 14)
      - Emspak Telegram Regarding Membership Meeting, April 27, 1943; 15. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 15)
      - Nathan Geller Regarding Finances, November 12, 1941; 16. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 16)
      - R. Linsley Regarding Sylvania Organization, March 24, 1942; 17. (Box 4, Folder 14, Item 17)
    - Local 502 Business Agent Larry Ryan Incoming Correspondence, October 31, 1941 - May 14, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - James Matles Regarding Local 502 Stackpole Carbon Collective Bargaining, October 31, 1941; 1. (Box 4, Folder 15, Item 1)
      - Secretary to Matles Regarding Local 502 Stackpole Carbon Contracts, November 18, 1941; 2. (Box 4, Folder 15, Item 2)
      - Secretary to Matles Regarding Wages and Local 1225, November 19, 1941; 3. (Box 4, Folder 15, Item 3)
      - Matles Regarding Local 502 Stackpole Carbon Contract and Sylvania Organization, November 25, 1941; 4. (Box 4, Folder 15, Item 4)
      - Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board and UE News, December 12, 1941; 5. (Box 4, Folder 15, Item 5)
      - Matles Regarding Stackpole Carbon, December 16, 1941; 6. (Box 4, Folder 15, Item 6)
      - Matles Regarding Staff Finances and Sylvania Tool Organization, January 13, 1942; 7. (Box 4, Folder 15, Item 7)
      - Matles Regarding Sylvania Organization, January 23, 1942; 8. (Box 4, Folder 15, Item 8)
      - Matles Regarding Staff Finances, May 6, 1942; 9. (Box 4, Folder 15, Item 9)
      - Matles Regarding United Construction Workers Organizing Committee, May 20, 1942; 10. (Box 4, Folder 15, Item 10)
      - Matles Regarding Overtime and Local 502 Contract, December 30, 1942; 11. (Box 4, Folder 15, Item 11)
      - Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 14, 1943; 12. (Box 4, Folder 15, Item 12)
    - Local 502 Business Agent Larry Ryan Outgoing Correspondence, October 20 - December 23, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Ryan Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding Stackpole Carbon, October 20, 1941; 1. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 1)
      - Ryan Telegram to James Matles Regarding Local 502 Stackpole Carbon Collective Bargaining, October 29, 1941; 2. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 2)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding St. Mary's and Emporium Sylvania Organization, October 30, 1941; 3. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 3)
      - Ryan to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 4, 1941; 4. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 4)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Stackpole Collective Bargaining, Wages and Carbon Industry, November 13, 1941; 5. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 5)
      - Ryan Telegram to UE Regarding Local 502 Stackpole Carbon Contract, November 15, 1941; 6. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 6)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Local 502 Stackpole Carbon Contract, Organization and Elections with L. G. Hall Letter to Local 502 Negotiating Committee, November 17, 1941; 7. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 7)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Wages and Organization at Speer Carbon and Sylvania, November 19, 1941; 8. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 8)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Local 502 Constitution, November 25, 1941; 9. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 9)
      - Ryan to Emspak Regarding Stackpole Carbon, November 28, 1941; 10. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 10)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Emporium Sylvania Organization, November 28, 1941; 11. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 11)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, December 3, 1941; 12. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 12)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Sylvania Organization, Membership and Workers Educational, December 3, 1941; 13. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 13)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Chicago Conference, December 9, 1941; 14. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 14)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Supplies and UE News, December 11, 1941; 15. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 15)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Finances, National Labor Relations Board and Public Assistance, December 15, 1941; 16. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 16)
      - Ryan to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 18, 1941; 17. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 17)
      - Ryan to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 23, 1941; 18. (Box 4, Folder 16, Item 18)
    - Local 502 Business Agent Larry Ryan Outgoing Correspondence, January 3 - October 14, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Ryan to James Matles Regarding Radio Industry and Chicago Conference, January 3, 1942; 1. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 1)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, January 14, 1942; 2. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 2)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Local 502 Speer Carbon Contract, January 17, 1942; 3. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 3)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Staff Finances and Sylvania Organization, January 27, 1942; 4. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 4)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Emporium and Salem Sylvania Organization, March 4, 1942; 5. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 5)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Radio Conference, April 15, 1942; 6. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 6)
      - Ryan to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, April 25, 1942; 7. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 7)
      - Ryan to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, April 29, 1942; 8. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 8)
      - Ryan to Emspak Regarding Supplies, May 11, 1942; 9. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 9)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding District 50 and Construction Workers Organizing Committee, May 14, 1942; 10. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 10)
      - Ryan to Emspak Regarding Bakelite Industry and Organization, May 19, 1942; 11. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 11)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding District 50, Construction Workers Organizing Committee and Stewards Classes, May 19, 1942; 12. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 12)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Construction Workers Organizing Committee and Sylvania Plants in Emporium, Mill Hall, and Williamsport, May 22, 1942; 13. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 13)
      - Ryan to Research Department Regarding Organizers Bulletin, September 16, 1942; 14. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 14)
      - Ryan Telegram to Matles Regarding Local 502 Speer Carbon Contract, September 21, 1942; 15. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 15)
      - Ryan to Emspak Regarding Executive Order 9240 and Overtime, October 3, 1942; 16. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 16)
      - Ryan to Emspak Regarding Executive Order 9240 and Overtime, October 14, 1942; 17. (Box 4, Folder 17, Item 17)
    - Local 502 Business Agent Larry Ryan Outgoing Correspondence, November 7, 1942 - July 16, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Ryan to James Matles Regarding Clearfield Organization, November 7, 1942; 1. (Box 4, Folder 18, Item 1)
      - Ryan to Julius Emspak Regarding Overtime, November 13, 1942; 2. (Box 4, Folder 18, Item 2)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Airplane and Marine Instruments, November 16, 1942; 3. (Box 4, Folder 18, Item 3)
      - Ryan to Emspak Regarding Executive Order 9240 and Overtime, November 19, 1942; 4. (Box 4, Folder 18, Item 4)
      - Ryan to Emspak Regarding Executive Order 9240, Overtime and No-Strike Pledge, November 28, 1942; 5. (Box 4, Folder 18, Item 5)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Stackpole Carbon Contract, January 11, 1943; 6. (Box 4, Folder 18, Item 6)
      - Ryan to Organizational Department Regarding Organizational Bulletins, February 3, 1943; 7. (Box 4, Folder 18, Item 7)
      - Ryan to Requisition Department Regarding Executive Order 9240, February 12, 1943; 8. (Box 4, Folder 18, Item 8)
      - Ryan to Emspak Regarding Town Meeting, April 12, 1943; 9. (Box 4, Folder 18, Item 9)
      - Ryan to James Byrnes Regarding Executive Order 9240, Overtime and Absenteeism, April 19, 1943; 10. (Box 4, Folder 18, Item 10)
      - Ryan to Matles Regarding Conscription and Staff Members, May 11, 1943; 11. (Box 4, Folder 18, Item 11)
      - Ryan Telegram to Matles Regarding Local 502 Speer Carbon Strike, June 16, 1943; 12. (Box 4, Folder 18, Item 12)
      - Ryan Telegram to Matles Regarding Speer Carbon National Labor Relations Board Election, July 16, 1943; 13. (Box 4, Folder 18, Item 13)
    - Local 502 General Incoming Correspondence, October 10, 1940 - December 23, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - William Chambers to Eugene Kraus Regarding Staff Members, October 17, 1941; 1. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 1)
      - Chambers to John McGuire Regarding Cameron Manufacturing, December 7, 1943; 2. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 2)
      - John Daly to McGuire Regarding War Labor Board, Stackpole Carbon and Speer Carbon with April 7, 1944, Daly Letters to David Schribner and Albert Fitzgerald, April 18, 1944; 3. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 3)
      - Julius Emspak to Max Horvatin Regarding UE News, October 10, 1940; 4. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 4)
      - Emspak to Horvatin Regarding Membership Lists, December 27, 1940; 5. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 5)
      - Emspak to Eugene Kraus Regarding Finances, January 2, 1941; 6. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 6)
      - Emspak to Marion Brown Regarding UE News, December 15, 1941; 7. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 7)
      - Emspak to Chambers Regarding Clearfield Charter, January 21, 1943; 8. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 8)
      - Emspak to Clair Kester Regarding Clearfield Charter, January 27, 1943; 9. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 9)
      - Emspak to Hohn McGuire Regarding Cameron Manufacturing, December 6, 1943; 10. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 10)
      - Emspak Telegram to McGuire, April 4, 1944; 11. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 11)
      - Emspak to S. J. Jesberger Regarding Local 105, April 3, 1946; 12. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 12)
      - Emspak to T. J. Moriarity Regarding Post Office, September 11, 1945; 13. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 13)
      - Emspak to Jesberger Regarding Veterans and Finances, November 10, 1945; 14. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 14)
      - Emspak to John Wegemer Regarding Local 502 Strike, May 11, 1946; 15. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 15)
      - Helen Lief, Secretary to Emspak, to Jesberger Regarding Factionalism, May 29, 1946; 16. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 16)
      - Emspak to Jesberger Regarding Factionalism, July 2, 1946; 17. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 17)
      - Emspak to Alfred Oyler Regarding Constitutions, August 23, 1946; 18. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 18)
      - Emspak to Jesberger Regarding Punxsutawney Speer Carbon Organization, June 2, 1947; 19. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 19)
      - Emspak to Jesberger Regarding Supplies, June 12, 1947; 20. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 20)
      - Emspak to Jesberger Regarding Dues Check-Off and Supplies, December 23, 1947; 21. (Box 4, Folder 19, Item 21)
    - Local 502 General Incoming Correspondence, February 4, 1941 - October 20, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Julius Emspak to S. J. Jesberger Regarding Solar Electric Strike, January 7, 1948; 1. (Box 4, Folder 20, Item 1)
      - Emspak to Jesberger Regarding Local 502 Molded Materials Arbitration, January 13, 1948; 2. (Box 4, Folder 20, Item 2)
      - Emspak to John Grotzinger Regarding 1948 UE Convention, September 23, 1948; 3. (Box 4, Folder 20, Item 3)
      - Emspak to Ed Ehrensberger Regarding Factionalism and Davido and Brehm Case, July 1, 1949; 4. (Box 4, Folder 20, Item 4)
      - Emspak to John Wegemer Regarding Factionalism and Davido and Brehm Case, October 20, 1949; 5. (Box 4, Folder 20, Item 5)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to George Clouser Regarding Local 502 Molded Materials Collective Bargaining, July 6, 1948; 6. (Box 4, Folder 20, Item 6)
      - E. J. Hammer to Jesberger Regarding Stackpole Carbon and Dues Check-Off, August 3, 1945; 7. (Box 4, Folder 20, Item 7)
      - Frederick Livingston to Jesberger Regarding Local 502 Stackpole Carbon Arbitration, March 28, 1945; 8. (Box 4, Folder 20, Item 8)
      - James Matles to Francis Seth Regarding International Typographical Union with January 30, 1941, Woodruff Randoph Letter to Matles, February 4, 1941; 9. (Box 4, Folder 20, Item 9)
      - Secretary to Matles Letter, April 2, 1941; 10. (Box 4, Folder 20, Item 10)
      - Matles to Eugene Kraus Regarding Local 502 Stackpole Carbon Contract, October 9, 1941; 11. (Box 4, Folder 20, Item 11)
      - Matles to Kraus Regarding Staff Finances, December 4, 1941; 12. (Box 4, Folder 20, Item 12)
      - Matles to Jesberger Regarding Carbon Industry with Matles Letters to Sidney Gilbert, Peter Besch, Walter Berry, and Leonard Lewin and November 15, 1945, Matles Letter to Leo Turner, November 13, 1945; 13. (Box 4, Folder 20, Item 13)
      - Matles to Jesberger Regarding Powder Metallurgy with November 15, 1945, Sidney Gilbert Letter to Matles, November 23, 1945; 14. (Box 4, Folder 20, Item 14)
    - Local 502 General Incoming Correspondence, August 27, 1943 - June 15, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - James Matles to John Grotzinger Regarding Factionalism with Matles Letter to Charles Newell, June 15, 1949; 1. (Box 4, Folder 21, Item 1)
      - Russ Nixon to John McGuire Regarding Cameron Manufacturing and War Production with December 20, 1943, Nixon Memo to Julius Emspak, December 17, 1943; 2. (Box 4, Folder 21, Item 2)
      - Nixon to Sylvester Jesberger Regarding AFL-CIO Unity with February 18, 1947, Philip Murray Letter to William Green, February 19, 1947; 3. (Box 4, Folder 21, Item 3)
      - David Ratner to Jesberger Regarding Group Insurance, July 11, 1946; 4. (Box 4, Folder 21, Item 4)
      - David Schribner to McGuire, March 29, 1944; 5. (Box 4, Folder 21, Item 5)
      - Schribner to Jesberger Regarding Dues Check-Off, August 20, 1945; 6. (Box 4, Folder 21, Item 6)
      - A. N. Towsen to Eugene Kraus Regarding Wages, August 27, 1943; 7. (Box 4, Folder 21, Item 7)
    - Local 502 General Outgoing Correspondence, February 13, 1947 - August 5, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - George Clouser to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Taft-Hartley Affidavits, May 14, 1948; 1. (Box 4, Folder 22, Item 1)
      - Clouser to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 502 Molded Materials Strike with July 1, 1948, Fitzgerald Letter to Charles Newell, June 28, 1948; 2. (Box 4, Folder 22, Item 2)
      - Ed Ehrensberger to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Taft-Hartley Affidavits, April 15, 1948; 3. (Box 4, Folder 22, Item 3)
      - Ehrensberger to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, April 16, 1948; 4. (Box 4, Folder 22, Item 4)
      - Ehrensberger to Newell Regarding Factionalism, March 25, 1949; 5. (Box 4, Folder 22, Item 5)
      - Ehrensberger to Stanley Loney Regarding Factionalism, March 25, 1949; 6. (Box 4, Folder 22, Item 6)
      - Ehrensberger to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Davido-Brehm Case with June 23, 1949, Fitzgerald Letter to Loney, June 20, 1949; 7. (Box 4, Folder 22, Item 7)
      - Ehrensberger to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Davido-Brehm Case, August 5, 1949; 8. (Box 4, Folder 22, Item 8)
      - John Grotzinger to Emspak Regarding 1948 UE Convention, September 15, 1948; 9. (Box 4, Folder 22, Item 9)
      - Grotzinger to James Matles Regarding Factionalism, June 13, 1949; 10. (Box 4, Folder 22, Item 10)
      - Jacob Heiberger to Emspak Regarding Local 502 Stackpole Carbon Strike and Factionalism with February 25, 1947, Emspak Letter to Thomas Fitzpatrick, February 13, 1947; 11. (Box 4, Folder 22, Item 11)
    - Local 502 General Outgoing Correspondence, October 5, 1945 - December 30, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Sylvester J. Jesberger to UE Regarding Staff Members, October 5, 1944; 1. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 1)
      - Jesberger to A. E. Kronenwetter Regarding Dues Check-Off, July 26, 1945; 2. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 2)
      - Jesberger to David Schribner Regarding Foremen and Dues Check-Off with Local 502 Stackpole Carbon Contract, August 8, 1945; 3. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 3)
      - Jesberger to James Matles Regarding Carbon Industry Organization with Carbon Plant List, November 6, 1945; 4. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 4)
      - Jesberger to Julius Emspak Regarding Veterans and Finances, November 8, 1945; 5. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 5)
      - Jesberger Letter to Emspak, February 20, 1946; 6. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 6)
      - Jesberger Telegram to Emspak Regarding Local 502, April 3, 1946; 7. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 7)
      - Jesberger to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, May 21, 1946; 8. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 8)
      - Jesberger to Helen Leif Regarding Factionalism, June 4, 1946; 9. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 9)
      - Jesberger to Emsapk Regarding Local 502 Strike, July 17, 1946; 10. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 10)
      - Jesberger to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, January 13, 1947; 11. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 11)
      - Jesberger to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Local 502 Strike, March 11, 1947; 12. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 12)
      - Jesberger to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and CIO Southern Organizing Drive, March 25, 1947; 13. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 13)
      - Jesberger to Emspak Regarding Punxsutawney Speer Carbon Organization and District 50 with May 16, 1947, Emspak Letter to Thomas Fitzpatrick, May 14, 1947; 14. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 14)
      - Jesberger to Emspak Regarding Supplies, May 28, 1947; 15. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 15)
      - Jesberger to Emspak Regarding Supplies with Membership Card, December 16, 1947; 16. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 16)
      - Jesberger to Emspak Regarding Local 633 Solar Electric Strike with December 22, 1947, Fitzpatrick Letter to All Local Unions, December 30, 1947; 17. (Box 4, Folder 23, Item 17)
    - Local 502 General Outgoing Correspondence, December 30, 1940 - January 9, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Sylvester Jesberger to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 502 Molded Materials with January 5, 1948, Jesberger Letter to Joseph Brandschain, January 9, 1948; 1. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 1)
      - Clair Kester to UE Regarding Airplane and Marine Instruments Charter and Contract and the War Labor Board, January 16, 1943; 2. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 2)
      - Kester to Emspak Regarding Airplane and Marine Instruments Charter, June 17, 1943; 3. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 3)
      - Eugene Kraus to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 30, 1940; 4. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 4)
      - Kraus to James Matles Regarding American Peace Conference, March 31, 1941; 5. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 5)
      - Kraus to Matles Regarding Local 502 Stackpole Carbon Collective Bargaining with UE News Reprint, October 6, 1941; 6. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 6)
      - Louise Maher to Emspak Regarding Local 502 Strike and Finances, April 5, 1946; 7. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 7)
      - John McGuire to Matles Regarding Smethport and Emporium Organization and Fur and Leather Workers, September 29, 1943; 8. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 8)
      - Matles to Emspak Regarding Cameron Manufacturing, December 1, 1943; 9. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 9)
      - Matles to Russ Nixon Regarding Cameron Manufacturing and Reconversion, December 13, 1943; 10. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 10)
      - Matles to Nixon Regarding Cameron Manufacturing and Reconversion with January 7-8, 1944, Drew Pearson Columns, January 8, 1944; 11. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 11)
      - Matles to Alfred Oyler Regarding Finances, February 24, 1944; 12. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 12)
      - Matles to Harold Briney Regarding Cameron Manufacturing and Unemployment, March 8, 1944; 13. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 13)
      - Matles to Emspak Regarding Finances, Unemployment and Cameron Manufacturing Speer Resistor, March 8, 1944; 14. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 14)
      - Matles to Michael Fitzpatrick Regarding Fourth War Loan Drive and Factionalism, March 8, 1944; 15. (Box 4, Folder 24, Item 15)